<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
  ~ This file is part of Amproid
  ~
  ~ Copyright (c) 2019. Peter Papp
  ~
  ~ Please visit https://github.com/4phun/Amproid for details
  ~
  ~ Amproid is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ Amproid is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with Amproid. If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/
  -->


<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>

    <string name="account_add_button_label">Add</string>
    <string name="account_add_dialog_title">Add account</string>
    <string name="account_manage_button_label">Manage</string>
    <string name="account_select_button_label">Select</string>
    <string name="account_select_label">Select account</string>
    <string name="psw_input_label">Password</string>
    <string name="url_input_label">Ampache server URL</string>
    <string name="user_input_label">User name</string>
    <string name="search_label">Search for</string>
    <string name="seek_bar_label">Seek Bar</string>

    <string name="clear_text_warning">Note: only secure \"https://\" connections allowed.</string>

    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="artist">Artist</string>
    <string name="art">Art</string>

    <string name="prev">Previous</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>

    <string name="accounts">Accounts</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_title">Amproid v%s</string>
    <string name="about_text" tools:ignore="PluralsCandidate">Ampache client for Android\n\nCopyright © 2019-%d Peter Papp\n\nhttps://github.com/4phun/Amproid"</string>
    <string name="now_playing">Now Playing</string>
    <string name="qsg">Quick Start Guide</string>

    <string name="equalizer">Equalizer</string>
    <string name="loudness">Loudness</string>

    <string name="hide_dot_playlists">Hide playlists whose name starts with a dot</string>

    <string name="tracks">Tracks</string>

    <string name="error_invalid_user_input">Invalid data entered</string>
    <string name="error_search_input_insufficient">Search expression too short. Minimum 3 characters needed.</string>

    <string name="license"><![CDATA[
Licensing
\n\n
Amproid is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.
\n\n
Amproid is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.
\n\n
You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with Amproid. If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/
    ]]></string>

    <string name="qsg_text"><![CDATA[
Amproid is an independently developed audio client for the
Ampache (https://ampache.org) media server. It is NOT a
streaming service. To use Amproid, it must be connected to your
Ampache instance.
\n\n\n
Connecting to your Ampache server
\n\n
When you first start Amproid, the Add Account dialog is displayed
automatically. Otherwise, tap Accounts in the menu, then tap Add.
Enter the server\'s URL, your user name, and your password, followed
by OK. Amproid attempts to connect to the server immediately.
Passwords are stored securely in Android’s Account manager.
\n\n\n
Exploring and playing content
\n\n
Amproid provides four tabs to help you explore the contents on your
Ampache server:
\n\n
For You offers recommendations based on your favorites and your
listening history. You can tap the refresh button to get a new set of
recommendations.
\n\n
Search Results displays the results of your last search. You can search
either by tapping the magnifying glass icon, or using Google Assistant.
In the latter case, Amproid automatically starts playing a close match
when the search completes.
\n\n
Playlists shows all playlists and smart list created on your server.
When you first click this tab, Amproid downloads and caches this list.
Tap the refresh button to have the list downloaded again, for example if
you create a new playlist or smart list on your server.
\n\n
New shows a list of recently added albums.
\n\n\n
Now Playing
\n\n
This tab displays details of the currently playing track, such as the
album art, title, artist, and album. When you’re playing an entire album
or playlist, you can also tap the title to display the list of tracks,
where you can tap a track to play it straight away.
\n
    ]]></string>

</resources>